Let's get back to the interpretation of the factor return.
再回到因子收益率上
When initially learning about alpha factors,
一开始学习 alpha 因子时
the magnitude of the return can create some confusion.
收益率大小容易让人困惑
In the alphas we work with below the annual returns range from 1%-4% or so.
在下面的 alpha 中 年度收益率的范围是从 1% 到 4% 左右
Let's be honest, that seems really small,
说实话 看起来很小
is that what institutions really want from their researchers?
机构就希望他们的研究员获得这么小的收益率？
The key to placing these returns and context is to understand the concept of
了解这些收益率的关键是
the return denominator in research and
了解研究领域的收益率分母
the actual leverage likely to be used in production trading.
以及在生产交易中可能会使用的实际杠杆效应
Let's first define return denominator,
先来定义下收益率分母
when we normalize an alpha vector one of the steps
当我们标准化 alpha 因子时
is to sum up the absolute values of the alpha values,
有个步骤是将 alpha 值的绝对值相加
then divide each value by the sum in order for
然后使每个值除以这个和
the normalized vector to have the sum of absolute values equal to one.
从而让标准化向量的绝对值之和等于 1
The sum of the absolute magnitudes of
alpha 值的绝对大小之和
the alpha values is the denominator that I'm referring to.
就是我说的分母
Leverage is the act of borrowing money in order to take positions in assets like stocks.
杠杆作用是指借贷资金来对股票资产建仓
The leverage ratio is the sum of the absolute value of all positions long and
杠杆比率是指所有做多和做空头寸的绝对值之和
short divided by whatever capital we actually devote to supporting those positions.
除以我们为这些头寸投入的资金
This concept will likely become more clear when we study backtesting in term two,
当我们在第二学期学习回溯测试时 这个概念会更清晰
until then, think about it this way,
在此之前 先这么思考
a trading strategy produces dollars of gains and losses,
交易策略会产生损益金额
to convert those dollars in terms of returns or in return space,
为了将这些金额转换成收益率或收益率空间
we need to divide by some denominator,
我们需要除以某个分母
which in this case is called the capital denominator.
在此情形下称为资本分母
At the research stage,
在研究阶段
we ignore this and simply assume one dollar of capital to one dollar of longs and shorts.
我们会忽略这一点 并直接假定一美元资金对应一美元做多和做空头寸
When we increase leverage by putting
当我们增加杠杆作用
less than one dollar of capital against one dollar of positions,
并将不到一美元的资金投入一美元的头寸上时
the leverage ratio increases.
杠杆比率会增大
A leverage ratio of one means we apply one dollar of capital for one dollar of positions.
杠杆比率为 1 表示我们针对一美元的头寸投入一美元资金
A leverage ratio of four means,
杠杆比率为 4 表示
we apply 25 cents of capital for one dollar of positions.
我们针对一美元头寸投入 25 美分资金
In research, we are looking at the return of the normalized alpha factor,
在研究中 我们观察的是标准化 alpha 因子的收益率
the denominator is one,
所以分母为 1
which implies a leverage ratio of one.
表示杠杆比率为 1
In a real trading,
在实际交易中
we would combine several factors and then apply leverage,
我们会整合多个因子 然后应用杠杆
depending on the final portfolio,
根据最终的投资组合
an institution might apply leverage of anywhere from two times to six times.
投资机构可能会应用 2x-6x 的杠杆
In the context of that leverage the magnitude of the alpha factor returns start to make
在这么大的杠杆比率下 alpha 因子收益率的大小
sense and likely look comparable to
开始变得合理起来
the published returns observable from hedge fund return indices.
并且与对冲基金收益率指数发布的收益率相当
This insight should also help explain why I continually
这一点也解释了我为何不断
refer to implementing this style of trading as inside an asset management firm.
将这种交易风格视为仅在资产管理企业内发生
It would be very unlikely that an individual,
个人很难获得
could obtain the necessary leverage and
必要的杠杆和低成本市场机会
low-cost market access to allow him or her to trade in this style,
能够在个人经纪帐户里
in an individual brokerage account.
以这种方式交易